http://www.corrotherm.co.uk/policy/privacy

Applications
Corrosion Resistant INCONEL INCOLOY And MONEL Marine Applications
Electrical Resistance Alloys INCOLOY INCONEL RESISTOHM-BRIGHTRAY
Applications
Corrosion Resistant INCONEL INCOLOY And MONEL Marine Applications
Electrical Resistance Alloys INCOLOY INCONEL RESISTOHM-BRIGHTRAY
Contact
Privacy policyWhile the policy statement below covers the fine detail, we can sum it up as follows. We will respect and protect your privacy. We won’t publish, give, sell or rent the Corrotherm International contact list to anyone without your prior consent. We don’t abuse the trust you place in us when you send us an enquiry.
The fine detail
This policy statement tells you how we collect information from you and how we use it. This statement forms part of our web site Terms and Conditions.
The information you provide is used to make your visits to our site easy and enjoyable. Be assured that we will not disclose your personal information to third parties without your consent. However, we reserve the right to disclose user information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) Corrotherm International’s rights or property, other users, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. We also reserve the right to disclose user information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it.
We collect aggregate information about our subscribers and web visitors. This data may be used to customise Corrotherm web content to deliver a better experience for our users and will in no way personally identify you.
We do request personal information such as your name and email address when you subscribe to our newsletters or send us a message from our contact form. We need to collect this information for personalisation and delivery and/or for purposes of editorial content and decisions.
Furthermore, we may use your personal information to send you periodic Corrotherm International communications, solicit your feedback, provide you with special offers, or for other purposes relating to our business. If you choose to opt out of receiving any communications from us, please use the unsubscribe link at the foot of any newsletter message we may send you.
The EU Cookie Law
A cookie is a small piece of data sent from web sites you visit – such as ours – and stored in your web browser. The EU Cookie Law states that, with some exceptions, web sites must not now create and set such cookies without your explicit permission first. In the spirit of working towards compliance we would like you to know the following.
Our web publishing software predates the EU Cookie Law and sets 3 cookies in your browser as part of its default behaviour. No information that identifies you personally is collected. The names and functions of these cookies are as follows:
exp_last_visit: this cookie records the date and time of your last visit, which will be today. Although it is set for all visitors it only supports functions for registered users. It will expire automatically in a year.
exp_last_activity: this cookie records the date and time of your last visit to our site prior to today. If this is your first visit, the date and time set will be as per exp_last_visit. It will expire automatically in a year.
exp_tracker: this cookie is more benign than it sounds. It merely records up to the last 5 pages you have visited on our site so that page redirection can be handled where appropriate. It will expire automatically when you quit your browser.
In addition to the above, our use of Google Analytics sets the following cookies:
__utma
__utmb
__utmc
__utmz
See Google’s explanation (for a technical audience) of how these are used.
If you wish to discuss this issue further, please contact us.
Use of IP address
An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web. Web servers automatically identify your computer by its IP address. We potentially collect IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, to analyse aggregate information, and to audit the use of our site. When visitors request web pages from Corrotherm, our servers log the visitors’ IP addresses.
Links to other sites/ ‘public’ areas
You should be aware that when you are on our web site, you could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. There are links to other sites from out web site pages that take you outside our service. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data or solicit personal information. The privacy policies of these other sites may significantly differ from ours. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of any other sites and cannot guarantee the security of any of your personal information collected there.
Security
Protecting the security of all personally-identifiable information associated with our guests is of the utmost concern to us. We exercise great care in providing secure transmission of your information from your PC to our servers. Once we receive your transmission, we will take reasonable precautions to ensure its security on our systems. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect our users’ personal information and privacy, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you disclose or transmit to us online and cannot be responsible for the theft, destruction, or inadvertent disclosure of your personal information.
Privacy policy for minors
We do not knowingly collect information from minors. If you are under 18, please do not provide any personal information to us.
The List Owner (the data controller)
The List Owner is Corrotherm International Ltd. You can contact us here.
Access to your own data
To be provided with a copy of your own personal data that the List Owner holds, and to contest and correct inaccuracies, or request that their personal data be deleted, please contact us and we will respond quickly. To unsubscribe from our newsletters, simply use the unsubscribe link provided in each edition.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this site, you signify your assent to this Corrotherm International Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use this site. The terms of this Privacy Policy may change from time to time without prior notice to you, so please check this page periodically for any changes. Your continued use of this site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.
UK
Email
Sales
or Shipping
Call +44 23­ 8074 8100
Fax +44 23 8074 8114
vCard
Worldwide offices
© 2002-2018 Corrotherm International Ltd, all rights reserved, E&OE
® INCONEL, INCOLOY, NIMONIC, MONEL, UDIMET and NILO are registered trademarks of Special Metals Corporation
